syntryx.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Syntryx, Inc.

_**Our commitment to user privacy: We monitor Websites – Not Consumers**_

This seven-point Privacy Policy is applicable to Syntryx, Inc. (Syntryx) and any other website that Syntryx owns and operates:

### 1\. Children Under 18

Syntryx does not intend to collect any personal information from anyone under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, you should not enter information on any Syntryx website and should ask a parent to do so for you. If you are under 18, Syntryx must have express written permission from a parent before you may use any Syntryx site. The authorizing parent must begin by emailing us, certifying the parent’s age and authority, and giving us express permission to acquire and retain any such personal information from you as we may normally obtain from Members of our sites.

### 2\. Information Collection

Syntryx will never ask you for your password except as a typical login procedure. Never post your password by email or anywhere else on the internet.

Syntryx does not collect personally identifiable information about you from any of its domains except when you specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis. For example, we might ask for such information when we run a contest or when you register for subscription services. Syntryx will make every effort to ensure that whatever information you provide will be maintained in a secure environment. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Syntryx cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Syntryx does not store secure billing information.

### 3\. Information Sharing

Syntryx will not sell or trade your personally identifiable information to third parties. Syntryx may disclose Member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Syntryx rights or property, other Syntryx Members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Syntryx discloses Member information only when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

### 4\. Information Use

You should be aware that Syntryx may sometimes permit third parties to offer services through our sites. Syntryx is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of any third party when providing personally identifiable information.

Syntryx collects IP Addresses for system administration, record keeping, and advertising reporting. Your IP address is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the internet. Syntryx servers log incoming IP addresses. Think of an IP address like your zip code; it tells us in general terms where you’re from, what youve done, and what youre doing.

You should be very cautious when you voluntarily disclose personal information (for example, name or email address) on bulletin boards, in chat areas, or the upload areas of any Syntryx site. That information, along with any other information you may disclose in your posting, can be collected, correlated, and used by third parties, and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Syntryx.

### 5\. Links to Other Sites

Syntryx may offer links to other sites. Syntryx has no control over these external sites or their content, and cannot be held responsible for any actions they may take or any information they might collect. You may arrive at one of these sites through clicking on a banner advertisement, as part of a co-branding arrangement, or simply by selecting a link on a Syntryx webpage. These sites might issue their own Cookies or collect data or personal information. Use caution when visiting an external site.

### 6\. Security

Syntryx is aware of your privacy-security concerns and strives to collect only as much data as is required to make your internet experience as satisfying and unobtrusive as possible.

The foregoing policies are effective as of 6 October, 2005. Syntryx reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. By using this site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Syntryx sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

### 7\. Syntryx Rights

Be aware of reserved Syntryx Rights governing use of all Syntryx sites. Syntryx reserves rights including but not limited to the following:

  * Right to deny access to Syntryx.com and other Syntryx websites;
  * Right to add or deduct Credits from Member accounts;
  * Right to create, modify or terminate Member accounts;
  * Right to contact Members about account status and any other matter;
  * Right to disclose Member information  _only_ when Syntryx believes in good faith that the law requires it.
